The relationship between creatives and clients is ancient.
From Leonardo da Vinci with the Medici family, to Frank Gehry with Bilbao and the Guggenheim.
But if there is something that has been kept intact during all these years,
is that creatives and clients don't understand each other sometimes.
But how can we reach understanding using a text that says nothing
into thousands of sketches that we show to our clients?
We are talking about Lorem Ipsum.
If Lorem Ipsum was used day by day in our lives, nobody could be understood.
Darling, we have to talk. It's about Lorem Ipsum.
You have the right to remain silent. All you say can be used against Lorem Ipsum.
What I feel for you is Lorem Ipsum. Sit on it.
That's why the Lorem Ipsum project is born.
An initiative which aims to turn this contentless text into a tool
to improve the relationship between creatives and clients.
And how does it work? Very easy.
Replace the Lorem Ipsum you usually use in your sketches for the client
by the manifest from the Lorem Ipsum project,
a message of affection and respect for the work done.
Or, if you dare, create a personalized Lorem Ipsum
with the message you want encrypted in the original Lorem Ipsum.
Approve me this print, please. My girlfriend is getting married tomorrow
and I expect that she does it with me.
Because when understanding is involved, nothing can prevent that a good idea goes ahead.
The Lorem Ipsum Project
A production of LOREM IPSUM